wtools.io 2019-02-17

# Privacy Policy - Web Tools

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. 

At wtools.io, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by wtools.io and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, wtools.io makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

wtools.io does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## No spam, spyware or spoofing

wtools.io never sends email SPAM to your inbox and never installs spyware on your personal computer. We share your concern about these practices and believes firmly in a consumer's rights and privacy. 

## Third Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

The advertisements appearing on our website from time to time are provided by a variety of our third party advertising partners. We only share website usage information about our users with reputable third party advertisers for the sole purpose of better targeting our website banner advertisements. 

## External Links

If any part of this website links you to other sites, those sites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.
